Sheldon, you got him in your sights. Fire!
He's charging his plasma rifle.
- I can't shoot now, I'm cloaking.
- Now, Raj, kill Sheldon.
(Raj:)I can't see him.
That's why they call it cloaking,
dead man.
(Leonard:)- Start throwing grenades.
- I'm all out.
Hey, guys, my friends and I
got tired of dancing...
(Penny(entering with three other sexy women):)...so we came over to have sex
with you.
Now, Raj, jump in the tank.
- We said no tanks.
- There are no rules in hell.
(Howard:)Son of a bitch.
Med-pack! I need a med-pack!
Told you.
(Leonard:)There's a sniper.
Use your rocket launcher.
(Raj:)All I've got is a needler
and I'm all out of ammo!
(Sheldon:)And now you're out of life.
[SOUNDS ON TV STOP]
(Sheldon:)- Why did you hit pause?
- I thought I heard something.
(Penny:)- What?
- No... Never mind.
Sorry, go.